Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Art and Real Estate Holding Companies Records, 1939, 1960-1982 and undated IA20011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Fine Arts Corporation, 1969-1982; Series II.; 3.6 Linear Feet (9 boxes)
  These records are organized into four subseries: Subseries II.A. Minutes, legal documents, and seal, 1970-1981; Subseries II.B. Art object records, 1950, 1966, 1970-1979; Subseries II.C. Financial records, 1968-1982; Subseries II.D. Insurance, 1970-1982.
  Records consist of minutes, agenda, legal documents, correspondence, memoranda, contracts, invoices, cancelled checks and check receipts, ledgers, tax returns, reports, and inventories, relating to the activities of Fine Arts Corporation, 1969-1982. The minutes and agendas document shareholder meetings of the Corporation; the legal documents record the liquidation of the Corporation. The records related to art objects document the removal of objects from Sutton Place (Getty's English estate) and Posta Vecchia (one of Getty's Italian properties) either for transfer to the J. Paul Getty Museum or for sale. The financial records detail financial activities of the Corporation through tax returns, documents concerning stock and bank accounts, and correspondence. The insurance records describe coverage for the assets (art objects) of the Corporation, issued by Lloyd's of London and Willis, Faber and Dumas.
  The Fine Arts Corporation was incorporated in Delaware in 1970 (for tax purposes), although its offices were in Los Angeles. Frank Whitworth was president and Norris Bramlett a principal officer. The Corporation was organized "to own and hold indefinitely certain art objects over which Mr. Getty wished to maintain control and indirect ownership." (Letter from Joseph Peeler to Michael Enright of Arthur Andersen, dated July 23, 1971.)
  The Certificate of Incorporation describes the purpose of the Corporation:
  "The nature of the business, or objects or purposes to be transacted, promoted, or carried on are: To buy, sell, reproduce, work, manufacture, manipulate and generally deal in and deal with, works of art, paintings, pictures, engravings, novelties, artists' supplies, books, periodicals and other publications and to manufacture, buy, sell, deal in and with all materials, supplies, appliances, apparatus or other articles necessary or convenient with the foregoing businesses, or any parts thereof, and to engage in any other business which may be necessary, incidental or proper to the exercise of any or all of the aforesaid purposes of the corporation."
  "The Chairman stated that this Corporation [Fine Arts Corporation] has been formed with an authorized capital of 2,000,000 shares, $1 par value, of which none had been issued, at the instance of Art Properties, Inc. ("Art Properties") in order that Art Properties might transfer to this Corporation certain paintings, furniture and other works of art owned by Art Properties and presently situated in England and Italy in exchange for the issuance by this Corporation to Art Properties of shares of its capital stock, $1 par value."
  Hundreds of items were transferred from Sutton Place in exchange for stock in Fine Arts Corporation. J. Paul Getty was the sole stockholder in the corporation. His personal belongings were owned by Fine Arts Corporation after his death in 1976.
  Fine Arts Corporation was liquidated in 1980.
  - Minutes, legal documents, and seal, Subseries II.A.; 0.6 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
    These records are arranged in general chronological and subject order.
    Records consist of minutes and agendas from shareholders meetings, letters, bills of sale, the certificate of incorporation, bylaws and other legal documents of the Fine Arts Corporation, 1970-1981. The minutes record the election of officers, discussions of the Corporation's financial status, and the purchase of works of art. Also included are records documenting the liquidation of the Corporation in 1980; and information about a lawsuit filed by Elizabeth Briant in which the Corporation was named as a plaintiff.
    See also Series IIC. Financial records.
    - Bylaws, stock certificate, certificate of incorporation, minutes of incorporators, March, 1970; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 1-2)
    - Shareholder and Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1970-1974; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 3-4)
    - Shareholder and Board of Directors meeting minutes, July 1970-1975; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 5-6)
    - Shareholder and Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1975-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 7-8)
    - Shareholder and Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1976-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 9-10)
    - Agenda, Director's meeting, circa 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, Director's of FAC meeting, October 30, 1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 12)
    - Letters re: reason for creating FAC (tax and legal info), 1971 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 13)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1970-1971 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 14)
    - Statement of ownership, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 15)
    - Liquidation correspondence and documents, 1980-1981 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 16)
    - Elizabeth Briant filming contract, 1972-1973 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 17)
    - Elizabeth Briant lawsuit, 1978; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 18-19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-01, Folder 20)
    - Corporate seal, circa 1960s (Box 1986.IA.38-01)
  - Art object records, 1950-1979; Subseries II.B.; 0.6 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
    These records are arranged in the original order of accession.
    Records consist of correspondence, inventories, reports, and loan agreement forms relating to the valuation of art objects owned by the Fine Arts Corporation, 1950, 1966, 1970-1979, located at Sutton Place, J. Paul Getty's estate in England, and in Italy, at Posta Vecchia. Some of the records concern the removal of art objects from these locations for transfer to the Museum, or for sale at Christie's in New York.
    See also Series IIA. Minutes and legal documents, and Series IIC. Financial records.
    - Inventory and appraisal of art objects at Sutton Place, 1977; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 1-2)
    - A.F. McKno, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 3)
    - Art objects, Sutton Place, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 4)
    - Art objects, Italy and Sutton Place, 1976-1979; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 5-7)
    - Inventory and correspondence related to removal of art objects in Italy, 1975-1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 8)
    - Art objects, Sutton Place, shipped to museum, 1970-1975; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 9-11)
    - Loan agreement forms, 1975-1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 12)
    - Art object schedules, England and Italy, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 13)
    - Art objects shipped from UK to NY for sale, 1977-1978; [5 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 14-18)
    - Sale, art objects, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 19)
    - Dividends in kind (silverware), 1950; 1966,; 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-02, Folder 20)
    - Notices of relocating art objects, 1971-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 1-2)
    - Getty Oil purchase of Sutton Place art objects, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: art objects, Italy, 1977-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 4-5)
  - Financial records, 1962-1982; Subseries II.C.; 2 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
    These records are arranged in general subject groupings.
    Records consist of correspondence, ledgers, legal documents, financial documents (including check receipts, cancelled checks, invoices, tax returns), and reports, regarding the financial activities of the Fine Arts Corporation, 1968-1982. The records describe the the Corporation's financial situation during this period in the form of financial statements and tax returns; document taxes in the United States and tax environments in England through tax returns, correspondence, and official documents; describe the issuing and transfer of stock in the Corporation; describe in part the liquidation of the Corporation; and record the day-to-day financial actvities as overseen by Norris Bramlett.
    - Financial statements, 1971-1975 (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 6)
    - Financial statements, 1972-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 7)
    - Financial statements, 1971-1980; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 8-10)
    - Legal and financial information, 1979-1982; [5 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 11-15)
    - Investments, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 16)
    - Investments, 1978-1980; [1 of 2] (Box 1986.IA.12-03, Folder 17)
    - Investments, 1978-1980; [2 of 2] (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 1)
    - Bills of sale, 1970-1974 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 2)
    - Information re: sale of art objects to Museum, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 3)
    - Sale of art objects, UK and Italy, 1976-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 4)
    - Zuccaro, Lady Weston, sale to Getty Oil, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 5)
    - Memos re: panel restoration, 1975 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 6)
    - Memos, documents re: transfer of stock, 1980; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 7-9)
    - Taxes and financial statements, 1968-1979; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 10-12)
    - Tax returns, 1980; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 13-14)
    - Taxes, 1970-1980; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 15-16)
    - Tax return worksheets, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-04, Folder 17)
    - Bank of America information, 1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 1)
    - Bank of America account, 1970-1977; [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 2-5)
    - Bank account, 1979-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 6)
    - Fine Arts (capital), Bank of America account, 1970-1976; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 7-8)
    - Invoices, 1970-1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 9)
    - Request for invoice, Araldo, 1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 10)
    - Norris Bramlett expenses, 1977-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous financial documents, 1971-1973 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous letters and financial documents, 1970-1974 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 13)
    - Check receipts:
      - Fine Arts Corp. capital account miscellaneous, 1971-1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 14)
      - Brugger Fine Arts and Transfer Co., Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 15)
      - Bruno Tartaglia, 1978-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 16)
      - W.J. Byrnes and Co., 1973-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 17)
      - Christie's, 1972; 1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 18)
      - CT Corp. System, 1970-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 19)
      - J. Paul Getty, 1971-1976; 1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 20)
      - Getty Oil Company, 1970-1978; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 21-22)
      - Johnson and Higgins, 1970-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 23)
      - A.F. McKno, 1976-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 24)
      - Lillian Malashko, 1976-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-05, Folder 25)
      - Minnehoma Corp., 1977-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous check receipts, 1975-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 2)
      - Musick, Peeler and Garrett, 1977-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of State (CA taxes), 1971-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 4)
      - Randco Enterprises, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 5)
      - Pietro Riccini, 1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 6)
      - T. Rogers and Co., 1972; 1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 7)
      - Secretary of State (DE taxes), 1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 8)
      - Eileen M. Vogler, 1977-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 9)
      - Void, 1975-1979 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 10)
      - Frank Whitworth, 1970-1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 11)
      - Gaiola Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 12)
    - Fine Arts Corporation ledger: cancelled checks, financial information/ledgers, receipts, 1970-1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-07)
    - Fine Arts Corporation ledger: cancelled checks, financial information/ledgers, receipts, 1977-Jul 1980 (Box 1986.IA.12-08)
  - Insurance, 1970-1982; Subseries II.D.; 0.4 Linear Feet (1 box)
    Records consist of correspondence and insurance policies for the Fine Arts Corporation, 1970-1982. The records detail objects covered by the various policies issued by Lloyd's of London and Willis, Faber and Dumas, as well as those removed from the policies (through sales).
    - Correspondence and insurance policy, 1970-1977; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 13-15)
    - Fine Arts insurance policy, Willis, Faber and Dumas, 1976 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 16)
    - Fine Arts policy, floater, Willis, Faber and Dumas, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 17)
    - Fine Arts floater and policies, Lloyd's, 1973-1974 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 18)
    - Fine Arts floater and policies, Lloyd's (copy), 1973-1974 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence and invoices re: fine arts floater, 1973-1978; [3 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 20-22)
    - Fine Arts floater, Lloyd's, 1979-1982 (Box 1986.IA.12-06, Folder 23)
- Gaiola Corporation and Italian properties, 1966-1980; undated; Series III.; 5.4 Linear Feet (9 boxes)
  These records are organized into three subseries: Subseries III.A. Minutes, legal documents, and seal, 1970-1980; Subseries III.B. Financial records, 1966-1980; Subseries III.C. Photographs, undated.
  Records consist of correspondence, memoranda, invoices, financial statements, investment records, check receipts, tax returns, bank statements, stock certificates, ledger sheets, legal documents, certificate of incorporation, certificate of dissolution, meeting minutes, maps, photographs, and clippings relating to Gaiola Corporation, 1966-1980 and undated. Gaiola was formed to manage the purchase, sale and maintenance of J. Paul Getty's two Italian properties, and the records describe the purchase and sale of the properties, their condition, and the day-to-day legal, administrative and financial activities of Gaiola.
  Gaiola Corporation was formed out of the liquidation of Art Properties Inc. in order to control Getty's real estate holdings in Italy. In 1966, J. Paul Getty purchased part of La Posta Vecchia, near Palo, and leased another portion of that property from its owner, Don Ladislao Odescalchi; the following year, 1967, Getty bought an island (Isola Gaiola) and nearby property off the coast of Naples from the Societe Magioralfra. On each part of the Gaiola property stood a house, one of which was in a state of disrepair.
  "Gaiola was organized to own and hold indefinitely stock of an Italian corporation, over which Mr. Getty wished to maintain control and indirect ownership." (Letter from Joseph Peeler to Michael Enright of Arthur Andersen, dated July 23, 1971.)
  Apparently Fine Arts Corporation maintained Italian offices at La Posta Vecchia, which was controlled by Gaiola. The relation to Gaiola is unclear, but it seems Gaiola was responsible strictly for real estate whereas Fine Arts Corporation dealt with art objects, furniture, etc., both in England (at Sutton Place) and in Italy.
  - Minutes, legal documents, and seal, Subseries III.A.; 0.4 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
    Records consist of board of directors and shareholders meeting minutes, certificate of incorporation, and certificate of dissolution, 1970-1980, of Gaiola Corporation. The meeting minutes describe the formation of the corporation, the election of officers, and the distribution of stock.
    See also Series IIIB. Financial records.
    - Binder/book with liquidation documents and board of directors meeting minutes, 1976-1977; 1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder loose in box)
    - Gaiola minutes, 1970-1977; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 1-2)
    - Certificate of incorporation, minutes, bylaws, 1970-1975; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 3-5)
    - Gaiola minutes, 1977 (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 6)
    - Gaiola dissolution papers, 1979-1980 (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 7)
    - Corporate seal, circa 1960s (Box 1986.IA.38-01)
  - Financial records, 1966-1980; Subseries III.B.; 4 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
    These records are organized into five subseries: Series IIIB1. Purchase and sale records, 1966-1979;Series IIIB2. Investments and financial statements, 1968-1979; Series IIIB3. Stock records, 1967-1978, undated; Series IIIB4. Tax records, 1968-1980; Series IIIB5. Bank information and expenses, 1970-1980.
    Records consist of correspondence, memoranda, invoices, financial statements, investment records, check receipts, tax returns, bank statements, stock certificates, ledger sheets, legal documents, meeting minutes, maps, photographs, and clippings, 1966-1980, of the Gaiola Corporation. The records describe the purchase, sale and rental of J. Paul Getty's properties in Italy, La Posta Vecchia (Palo) and Gaiola (Naples); Gaiola's financial status during the period of its incorporation; the sale of Magioralfra stock (Magioralfra was the Italian corporation that sold the Gaiola property to J. Paul Getty); taxes paid, profit and loss, and information on the valuation of the Italian properties; the condition of those properties, and the day-to-day financial activities of Gaiola.
    - Purchase and sale records, 1966-1979; Series III.B.1.; 2.22 Linear Feet 4 boxes and 1 flat file
      These records are generally arranged by property.
      Records consist of correspondence, financial statements, invoices, legal documents, maps, photographs, and clippings related to the purchase and sale of Gaiola's Italian properties, 1966-1979. J. Paul Getty, through Gaiola, purchased and rented two properties in Italy, La Posta Vecchia (Palo) and Gaiola (Naples). The Posta Vecchia property consisted of two parcels, one purchased outright by Getty, the other rented. The records describe the purchase, sale and rental of these properties.
      - "Castello" at Palo (rented), 1966-1973; [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 8-11)
        General note
        [La Posta Vecchia rented property map rehoused into Flat File 9.]
      - Italian property (new acquisition) (1,000 sq. metre land strip from Prince Ladislao Odescalchi), 1973 (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 12)
        [La Posta Vecchia purchased property map rehoused into Flat File 9.]
      - Insurance, Posta Vecchia, 1966-1967; 1977 (Box 1986.IA.13-1, Folder 13)
      - Posta Vecchia (purchased), 1966-1977; 1979; [6 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-2, Folder 1-6)
      - Posta Vecchia restoration notes, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-2, Folder 7)
      - Italian property, Societe Magioralfra, Villa Gaiola (Naples), 1967-1976; [8 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-2, Folder 8-15)
      - Stephen Garrett's reports on Gaiola to J. Paul Getty, 1968-1973; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-2, Folder 16-17)
      - Photographs of Gaiola by Stephen Garrett, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-7, Folder loose in box)
      - Sale of Italian property, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 1)
      - Sale, Magioralfra, 1977-1979; [5 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 2-6)
      - Sale of house, 1977-1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 7)
    - Investments and financial statements, 1968-1979; Series III.B.2.; 0.32 Linear Feet 1 box
      These records are arranged by record type.
      Records consist of financial statements, correspondence, and investment records, 1968-1979, of Gaiola Corporation. The records describe Gaiola's financial status during the period of its incorporation, including investment details, money transfers, and internal auditing.
      - Gaiola investments, 1978-1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 8)
      - Financial, 1968-1979; [8 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 9-16)
      - Financial statements, 1971-1975 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 17)
      - Financial statements, 1973-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 18-19)
      - Gaiola financial miscellaneous, 1970; 1976-1977 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 20)
    - Stock records, 1967-1978; Series III.B.3.; 0.12 Linear Feet 2 boxes
      These records are arranged primarily in the original order in which they were accessioned.
      Records consist of correspondence, stock certificates, ledger sheets, legal documents, and meeting minutes, 1967-1978 and undated, of Gaiola Corporation. The records describe the sale of Magioralfra stock; Magioralfra was the Italian corporation that sold the Gaiola property to J. Paul Getty. The stock was purchased by Art Properties, Inc., which in turn sold it to J. Paul and Gordon Getty.
      See also Series IIIA. Minutes and legal documents.
      - Sale of Magioralfra stock, 1977-1978 (Box 1986.IA.13-3, Folder 21)
      - Magioralfra S.r.l. stock, 1966-1978; [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 1-4)
      - Stock and transfer ledger, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 5)
      - Stock certificate ledger, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 6)
    - Tax records, Series III.B.4.; 0.4 Linear Feet 2 boxes
      These records are arranged generally in the original order of accession.
      Records consist of correspondence, tax returns, tax forms, and legal documents, 1968-1980, of Gaiola Corporation. The records detail taxes paid, profit and loss, and information on the valuation of the Italian properties for tax purposes.
      - Taxes and financial information, 1975-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 7-8)
      - Tax return, 1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 9)
      - Taxes, 1967-1980; [9 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-4, Folder 10-18)
      - Magioralfra–form 959, 1968-1974; 1978; [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 1-4)
      - Franchise tax board data, 1980 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 5)
    - Bank information and expense records, Series III.B.5.; 0.95 Linear Feet 2 boxes
      These records are arranged generally in original accession order.
      Records consist of letters, bank statements, ledger sheets, check receipts, and copies of stock certificates and investment reports, 1970-1980, of Gaiola Corporation. The records provide additional information on the dissolution of Gaiola, as well information in the form of check receipts on the day-to-day financial activities of the Corporation. The records also include information about payments made to Zsa Zsa Gabor as reimbursement for her expenses in regard to a trip she made to London for a charity event. It is not clear why these documents were included in the records of Gaiola.
      See also Series IIIB. Minutes and legal documents.
      - Bank of America closeout, 1980 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 6)
      - Bank of America account no. 03623-05188, 1970-1980 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 7)
      - Union Bank safe deposit box, 1971-1977; [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 8-11)
      - Norris Bramlett check receipts, 1970-1979; [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 12-13)
      - Frank Whitworth check receipts, 1970-1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous check receipts, 1972-1979; [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 15-17)
      - Non-banking forms CM, CQ-1, CQ-2, FC-3, FC-4, 1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 18)
      - Getty oil check receipts, 1970-1978 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 19)
      - Voided check receipts, 1971-1977 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 20)
      - Zsa Zsa Gabor (Eva), 1972 (Box 1986.IA.13-5, Folder 21)
      - Ledger with check receipts, cancelled check, and balance information, 1970-1979 (Box 1986.IA.13-6)
  - Photographs, 1970-1980; Subseries III.C.; 1 Linear Feet (1 box and 1 flat file)
    These records are arranged in no apparent order.